The mission that changes everything begins…
No Time to Die is a action, thriller, adventure
film directed by Cary Joji Fukunaga.
Bond has left active service and is enjoying a tranquil life in Jamaica.
His peace is short-lived when his old friend Felix Leiter
from the CIA turns up asking for help.
The mission to rescue a kidnapped scientist turns out to be far more treacherous than expected,
leading Bond onto the trail of a mysterious villain armed with dangerous new technology.
James Bond, played by Daniel Craig.
Madeleine, played by Léa Seydoux.
Lyutsifer Safin, played by Rami Malek.
Nomi, played by Lashana Lynch.
M, played by Ralph Fiennes.
Q, played by Ben Whishaw.
No Time to Die is a 2021 spy thriller film directed by Cary Joji Fukunaga from a screenplay he co-wrote with Neal
Purvis, Robert Wade and Phoebe Waller-Bridge, based on a story conceived by Purvis, Wade and Fukunaga.
The sequel to Spectre (2015), it is the twenty-fifth film in the James Bond series and the fifth
and final film to star Daniel Craig as the fictional British MI6 agent James Bond.
In addition to Craig, Léa Seydoux, Ben Whishaw, Naomie Harris, Jeffrey Wright, Christoph Waltz, Ralph Fiennes, and Rory Kinnear reprise their roles from
previous films, with Rami Malek, Lashana Lynch, Billy Magnussen, Ana de Armas, David Dencik, and Dali Benssalah appearing in new roles.
The story follows Bond, who, after leaving active service with MI6, is
recruited by the CIA to find a kidnapped scientist.
He eventually confronts a powerful and vengeful adversary
armed with a weapon capable of killing millions.
Development on the film began in 2016.
Danny Boyle was originally attached to direct and
co-write the screenplay with John Hodge.
Both left in August 2018 due to creative differences, and Fukunaga
was announced as Boyle's replacement one month later.
Most of the cast had signed on by April 2019.
Principal photography took place from April to October 2019.
No Time to Die is the only James Bond film starring Daniel Craig that was not co-produced by
Columbia Pictures, due to the expiration of a deal between Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer and Sony.
It is also the only Bond film to be distributed by United Artists
Releasing, a joint venture between MGM and Annapurna Pictures.
Billie Eilish performed the theme song "No Time to Die," with Hans Zimmer
composing the score and Steve Mazzaro serving as the score producer.
After being delayed by Boyle's departure and later by the COVID-19 pandemic, No Time to Die premiered at the Royal Albert Hall in
London on 28 September 2021, and was released in the United Kingdom on 30 September and in the United States on 8 October.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics and grossed over $774 million worldwide,
becoming the fourth-highest-grossing film of 2021 and the third-highest grossing Bond film.
In addition, it earned several other box-office record achievements, including
becoming the third-highest-grossing film of all time in the UK.
The film was nominated for three awards at the 94th Academy Awards, winning
Best Original Song, and received numerous other accolades.
On 20 February 2025, Amazon MGM Studios announced that it had gained full creative control of the James Bond franchise from Eon
Productions, making No Time to Die the final film in the series to be produced under the custodianship of Albert R.
Broccoli, Michael G.
Wilson or Barbara Broccoli.
The film explores themes of based on novel or
book, forgiveness, poison, spy, mi6.
The tone is intense.